Mom just left, she went to Guam.
لقد غادرت أمي للتو، وذهبت إلى غوام.
You and Aries should take care of yourselves.
ينبغي عليك أنت وبرج الحمل الاعتناء بأنفسكما.
Because it's just gonna be the two of us here,
لأنه سيكون هناك اثنان فقط هنا،
you can't leave without asking for permission.
لا يمكنك المغادرة دون طلب الإذن.
And you'll inform me about who you're hanging out with.
وسوف تخبرني من هو الشخص الذي تقضي وقتك معه.
Jasper Jean Mariano.
جاسبر جان ماريانو.
That's not mine.
هذا ليس لي.
Hey, Denzel. What are you doing there?
مرحبًا، دينزل، ماذا تفعل هناك؟
Two red lines...
خطين احمرين...
Positive!
إيجابي!
Denzel's pregnant?!
دينزل حامل؟!
Ah! Mr. Fernandez.
اه! السيد فرنانديز.
The test results came back negative.
وجاءت نتائج الاختبار سلبية.
Your faces!
وجوهكم!
I should've taken a video.
كان ينبغي لي أن ألتقط فيديو.
Have pity on me.
اشفق علي.
Is it really mine?
هل هي حقا ملكي؟
How could you ask me that?!
كيف يمكنك أن تسألني ذلك؟
- Denzel! - What are you doing here?
- دنزل! - ماذا تفعل هنا؟
What do you want to talk about?
ماذا تريد أن تتحدث عنه؟
What if you got your girlfriend pregnant? What will you do?
ماذا لو حملت صديقتك ؟ ماذا ستفعل؟
It's Denzel. He doesn't want to take responsibility for Grace.
إنه دينزل، وهو لا يريد أن يتحمل مسؤولية جريس.
Can you talk to him?
هل يمكنك التحدث معه؟
Thanks for taking me here.
شكرا على اصطحابي إلى هنا.
- Why are you here? - Jay-jay needs to talk to you.
- لماذا أنت هنا؟ - جاي جاي يحتاج إلى التحدث معك.
I just used Grace.
لقد استخدمت جريس فقط.
She won't forgive me once she finds out the truth.
لن تسامحني عندما تكتشف الحقيقة.
You're a liar.
أنت كاذب.
- Grace! - Grace, hey!
- نعمة! - نعمة، هي!
Get down from there!
انزل من هناك!
Hey!
يا!
- Please, let's talk about this! - Don't come near me!
- من فضلك دعنا نتحدث عن هذا! - لا تقترب مني!
Stay away!
ابقى بعيدا!
Grace, let's talk. Please, get down.
جريس، دعنا نتحدث. من فضلك، انزلي.
Grace, please!
نعمة من فضلك!
Your problems won't get solved this way.
لن يتم حل مشاكلك بهذه الطريقة.
I will really jump if you get close!
سأقفز حقا إذا اقتربت!
- Grace, please! - Grace!
- نعمة من فضلك! - نعمة!
Please don't do this!
من فضلك لا تفعل هذا!
I know you're hurting.
أعلم أنك تتألم.
And you feel like you're alone.
وتشعر وكأنك وحدك.
But open your heart.
ولكن افتح قلبك.
There are people who want to help you.
هناك أشخاص يريدون مساعدتك.
Don't give up. Don't lose hope.
لا تستسلم، لا تفقد الأمل.
Don't get trapped in the past.
لا تقع في فخ الماضي.
What's important is the present.
المهم هو الحاضر .
And what you'll do tomorrow.
وماذا ستفعل غدا .
Grace, please.
نعمة من فضلك.
I don't want to!
انا لا اريد ذلك!
Grace, please!
نعمة من فضلك!
Come on!
تعال!
We're wasting our time here!
نحن نضيع وقتنا هنا!
Just jump.
فقط اقفز.
Keif!
Keif!
- What's wrong with you?! - Go ahead! Jump!
- ماذا بك؟! - اذهب! اقفز!
- Keifer! - You're going to jump, right? Go ahead!
- كايفر! - أنت ستقفز، أليس كذلك؟ هيا!
- Grace, no. - No one cares about you anyway.
- جريس، لا. - لا أحد يهتم بك على أي حال.
That's not true.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
That's a lie!
هذه كذبة!
So, what's the matter?
إذن ما الأمر؟
Look.
ينظر.
I know you're used to hurting others.
أعرف أنك معتاد على إيذاء الآخرين.
But even the ones you love, you wanna hurt?
ولكن حتى من تحبهم، هل تريد أن تؤذيهم؟
Is that who you are?
هل هذا أنت؟
Huh, Grace Miller?
هاه، جريس ميلر؟
Grace, please, come down and let's talk about this.
جريس، من فضلك، تعالي لنتحدث عن هذا.
Grace, please, get down here.
جريس، من فضلك، انزل إلى هنا.
Grace, let's talk.
جريس، دعنا نتحدث.
Grace, please.
نعمة من فضلك.
Come down here, let's talk this through.
تعال إلى هنا، دعنا نتحدث في هذا الأمر.
Grace...
جمال...
We need to talk.
نحن بحاجة للتحدث.
Yes, we'll talk about this.
نعم، سنتحدث عن هذا.
Come now, stop crying.
تعال الآن، توقف عن البكاء.
I wish it were that easy.
أتمنى أن يكون الأمر بهذه السهولة.
I wish I also have someone beside me to dry my tears.
أتمنى أن يكون بجانبي شخص يجفف دموعي.
Daleng Dale Performed by: GAT
دالنغ ديل يؤديها: GAT.
That's nice!
هذا جميل!
So cool.
رائع جداً.
Denzel's not here. Maybe he and Grace are fixing their problems.
دينزل ليس هنا. ربما هو و جريس يحلان مشاكلهما.
Hey, Jerk.
مهلا أيها الأحمق.
I'm talking to you.
انا اتحدث معك.
- What are you doing? - Nothing.
- ماذا تفعل؟ - لا شيء.
You really enjoy meddling, huh?
هل تستمتع حقًا بالتدخل، أليس كذلك؟
You three, you're full of shit.
أنتم الثلاثة، أنتم مليئون بالهراء.
What do you mean? We're not doing anything.
ماذا تقصد؟ نحن لا نفعل شيئا.
Felix. Want some chocolate?
فيليكس هل تريد بعض الشوكولاتة؟
Here.
هنا.
Why is it that some people are saved, while some are not?
لماذا يخلص بعض الناس بينما لا يخلص البعض الآخر؟
What?
ماذا؟
I don't get it.
انا لم احصل عليها.
We saved Grace, right?
لقد أنقذنا جريس، أليس كذلك؟
Exactly.
بالضبط.
But my brother?
ولكن أخي؟
No one bothered saving him, Jay.
لم يكلف أحد نفسه عناء إنقاذه، جاي.
He's the one who didn't want to die. But nobody came to save him.
إنه الشخص الذي لم يرغب في الموت، لكن لم يأتي أحد لإنقاذه.
Has the world turned upside down?
هل انقلب العالم رأسا على عقب؟
What are you saying?
ماذا تقول؟
He was killed, Jay!
لقد قُتل، جاي!
Murdered!
مقتول!
By who?
بواسطة من؟
Aries!
بُرْجُ الحَمَل!
Your cousin.
ابن عمك.
Your murderer cousin, Jay!
ابن عمك القاتل، جاي!
He's the one who killed my brother!
هو الذي قتل أخي!
And all of you!
وكلكم!
Huh!
هاه!
All of you wanted to save Grace!
لقد أردتم جميعًا إنقاذ جريس!
But how about my brother? Huh!
ولكن ماذا عن أخي؟ هاه!
No one dared to save him!
لم يجرؤ أحد على انقاذه!
Just let him be, Jay. Give him space for now.
فقط دعه وشأنه، جاي. امنحه مساحة الآن.
Okay.
تمام.
Hey.
يا.
That "okay" wasn't sincere.
إن كلمة "حسنًا" لم تكن صادقة.
You're gonna go to him, right? I know you.
أنت ستذهب إليه، أليس كذلك؟ أنا أعرفك.
Don't do it, Jay. Just let him be.
لا تفعل ذلك يا جاي، دعه وشأنه.
Alright, fine. Not today.
حسناً، ليس اليوم.
But tell me where he usually goes to be alone.
ولكن أخبرني أين يذهب عادةً ليكون بمفرده.
Some place I can show up at, without annoying him.
مكان أستطيع أن أذهب إليه، دون أن أزعجه.
- I told you to give him space. - Come on, just tell me.
- قلت لك أن تعطيه المساحة. - هيا، فقط أخبرني.
- Please. - I can't.
- من فضلك. - لا أستطيع.
I have chocolates, by the way.
بالمناسبة، لدي شوكولاتة.
Let's chat later.
دعونا نتحدث لاحقا.
Okay.
تمام.
Uhm...
اممم...
If you want to say something just spit it out. What is it?
إذا كنت تريد أن تقول شيئًا ما، فما هو؟
Okay.
تمام.
The thing is...
الشيء هو...
Uhh... about...
اه... حول...
What is it now?
ما هو الآن؟
Do you know Felix's brother?
هل تعرف أخ فيليكس؟
Y-Yes.
ن-نعم.
What did you do to him?
ماذا فعلت له؟
It's none of your business. Stop snooping around.
هذا ليس من شأنك. توقف عن التجسس.
Aries, I'm getting caught in the middle of your fight.
برج الحمل، أنا أقع في وسط معركتك.
How can I not get involved?
كيف لا يمكنني المشاركة؟
What should I do, turn a blind eye?
ماذا يجب أن أفعل، أغض البصر؟
I need to hear it from you!
أريد أن أسمع ذلك منك!
Give me a break.
أعطني استراحة.
I want to know!
أريد أن أعرف!
What did you do to Section E for them to hate you so much?
ماذا فعلت للقسم E حتى يكرهونك بهذه الدرجة؟
What did you do to Felix's brother?
ماذا فعلت لأخي فيليكس؟
You really want to know, huh?
هل تريد حقًا أن تعرف، أليس كذلك؟
Is this what you want?
هل هذا ما تريد؟
Percy.
بيرسي.
Percy was his brother's name.
وكان اسم أخيه بيرسي.
And I'm not the one to blame for his death, okay?
وأنا لست المسؤول عن وفاته، أليس كذلك؟
Satisfied?
راضي؟
He's crying? Why?
هو يبكي؟ لماذا؟
I've never seen him cry before.
لم أرى أبدا أنه يبكي من قبل.
I didn't mean it. I just want to get to the truth.
لم أقصد ذلك، أريد فقط الوصول إلى الحقيقة.
Shoot! You're so good!
أطلق النار! أنت جيد جدًا!
You're the one who blew up without reason.
أنت من انفجرت بدون سبب.
I didn't know you're good at basketball.
لم أكن أعلم أنك جيد في كرة السلة.
I was in the varsity before. Why?
لقد كنت في الجامعة من قبل. لماذا؟
What do you need?
ماذا تحتاج؟
I just want to talk to you.
أريد فقط أن أتحدث معك.
How did you know about this place?
كيف عرفت بهذا المكان؟
You really went out of your way to come here, huh?
لقد بذلت قصارى جهدك لتأتي إلى هنا، أليس كذلك؟
Do you get some kind of kick from meddling?
هل تشعر ببعض الإثارة نتيجة التدخل؟
Then what should I do?
ثم ماذا يجب أن أفعل؟
You're the one who blew up without reason.
أنت من انفجرت بدون سبب.
Just leave.
فقط أرحل.
No. It was difficult biking to this place.
لا، لقد كان من الصعب ركوب الدراجة إلى هذا المكان.
You gotta talk to me!
يجب عليك التحدث معي!
Jay, please!
جاي، من فضلك!
Explain it to me.
اشرح لي ذلك.
Okay, you're mad at Aries.
حسنًا، أنت غاضب من برج الحمل.
But why do you have to get mad at me too?
ولكن لماذا عليك أن تغضب مني أيضًا؟
Because you remind me of him!
لأنك تذكريني به!
I see the person who destroyed my family!
أرى الشخص الذي دمر عائلتي!
I understand you're mad, but--
أنا أفهم أنك غاضب، ولكن...
You don't understand, Jay! Please!
أنت لا تفهم يا جاي! من فضلك!
Could you stop meddling in other people's lives?
هل بإمكانك التوقف عن التدخل في حياة الآخرين؟
As if you know everything!
وكأنك تعرف كل شيء!
I'm meddling because I need to!
أنا أتدخل لأنني بحاجة إلى ذلك!
You're meddling because that's just what you are!
أنت تتدخل لأن هذا هو ما أنت عليه فقط!
My stepbrother died because of Aries.
لقد مات أخي غير الشقيق بسبب برج الحمل.
And because of that, our parents separated.
وبسبب ذلك انفصل والدينا.
Sorry.
آسف.
But you don't have to get angry at me.
ولكن لا ينبغي لك أن تغضب مني.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I just can't help hating everyone that's close to him, Jay.
لا أستطيع أن أتوقف عن كره كل من هو قريب منه، جاي.
- Felix... - Jay, you don't have to explain.
- فيليكس... - جاي، ليس عليك أن تشرح.
I understand.
أفهم.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
I shouldn't have directed my anger towards you.
لا ينبغي لي أن أوجه غضبي نحوك.
That was wrong.
كان ذلك خطأ.
I know you want to ask more questions, Jay.
أعلم أنك تريد طرح المزيد من الأسئلة، جاي.
Ask away.
اسأل بعيدا.
But wouldn't it be better if we talk about it some other time?
ولكن أليس من الأفضل أن نتحدث عن هذا في وقت آخر؟
You know...
أنت تعرف
everything came back to me when we were at the bridge.
كل شيء عاد إليّ عندما كنا في الجسر.
Grace, don't do it!
نعمة، لا تفعل ذلك!
I know you're hurting. And you feel like you're alone.
أعلم أنك تتألم وتشعر أنك وحيد.
But open your heart.
ولكن افتح قلبك.
There are people who want to help you.
هناك أشخاص يريدون مساعدتك.
You know, you did good back there.
هل تعلم أنك قمت بعمل جيد هناك؟
I should've been happy that Grace was saved, but I can't help feeling envious...
كان ينبغي لي أن أكون سعيدة لأن جريس تم إنقاذها، لكن لا يمكنني أن أتوقف عن الشعور بالحسد...
Because I remembered my brother.
لأني تذكرت أخي.
I remembered my anger towards Aries.
تذكرت غضبي تجاه برج الحمل.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Even if I don't know what exactly happened.
حتى لو أنني لا أعرف ما حدث بالضبط.
I know you've been through a lot.
أعلم أنك مررت بالكثير.
You know, I'm a bit jealous of you.
هل تعلم أنني أشعر بالغيرة منك بعض الشيء؟
How does it feel to have an older brother?
كيف تشعر عندما يكون لديك أخ أكبر؟
You know, when you have someone that will protect you?
هل تعلم عندما يكون لديك شخص يحميك؟
Right?
يمين؟
The way you are, Jay, I don't think you need protection at all.
بالطريقة التي أنت عليها، جاي، لا أعتقد أنك بحاجة إلى الحماية على الإطلاق.
You're so fearless. I guess it should be the other way around.
أنت شجاع جدًا، أعتقد أنه ينبغي أن يكون الأمر على العكس.
How about this? We can be your brothers now, Jay.
ماذا عن هذا؟ يمكننا أن نكون إخوتك الآن، جاي.
- Shut up. I wanted protection, not stress. - Stress?
- اسكت، أردت الحماية، وليس التوتر. - التوتر؟
[laughs]
[يضحك]
Oh, by the way. Are you practicing for the festival?
بالمناسبة، هل تتدربين للمهرجان؟
What for? I'm not in the basketball team anymore.
لماذا؟ أنا لم أعد في فريق كرة السلة.
But you're so good. Such a waste.
لكنك جيد جدًا، يا له من إهدار.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
But...
لكن...
Aries got me kicked out of the team.
لقد تسبب برج الحمل في طردني من الفريق.
What? Aries again?
ماذا؟ برج الحمل مرة أخرى؟
Yeah.
نعم.
You know, I was shortlisted for students that will receive scholarship.
كما تعلمون، لقد تم اختياري من بين الطلاب الذين سيحصلون على المنح الدراسية.
But how could that happen if I'm not part of the basketball team.
ولكن كيف يمكن أن يحدث ذلك وأنا لست جزءًا من فريق كرة السلة.
I hope I can help you.
آمل أن أتمكن من مساعدتك.
I hope so too.
آمل ذلك أيضًا.
Why don't you just teach me basketball?
لماذا لا تعلميني كرة السلة؟
Basketball? You're so random.
كرة السلة؟ أنت عشوائي جدًا.
Can you keep up? What can you do?
هل تستطيع الاستمرار؟ ماذا تستطيع أن تفعل؟
- Run. - Run?
- أركض. - أركض؟
I'll show you. Come on!
سأريكم، هيا!
- Really? - See!
- حقا؟ - انظر!
Alright, one word. One word.
حسنًا، كلمة واحدة. كلمة واحدة.
Two syllables.
مقطعين لفظيين.
Chop, chop.
تقطيع، تقطيع.
Sir Alvin.
السير ألفين.
It's Sir Alvin!
إنه السير ألفين!
- David? - Who is that?
- ديفيد؟ - من هذا؟
Keifer!
كيفر!
[cheering]
[هتاف]
Now it's my turn. Wait a minute!
الآن جاء دوري، انتظر لحظة!
Let's do it this way - anyone who guesses wrong must pay five hundred!
دعونا نفعل ذلك بهذه الطريقة - أي شخص يخمن خطأ يجب أن يدفع خمسمائة!
[students complaining]
[الطلاب يشكون]
Alright, here I go. Okay, okay.
حسنًا، ها أنا ذا. حسنًا، حسنًا.
Wait. Wait.
انتظر انتظر.
- One word.
- كلمة واحدة.
- Two syllables. - Okay.
- مقطعين. - حسنًا.
Let's go, let's go.
دعنا نذهب، دعنا نذهب.
[laughs]
[يضحك]
- Chicken? - Chicken!
- دجاجة؟ - دجاجة!
Phoenix?
فينيكس؟
- Rory! - Yuri?
- روري! - يوري؟
- Did you answer that? - Is that right?
- هل أجبت على ذلك؟ - هل هذا صحيح؟
My brain's delayed, so yeah.
عقلي متأخر، لذلك نعم.
[cheering]
[هتاف]
How about this one?
ماذا عن هذا؟
- One word. - What's next?
- كلمة واحدة. - ماذا بعد؟
Two. Two syllables?
اثنان. مقطعين؟
- What's that? - Are you dancing?
- ما هذا؟ - هل ترقص؟
Rory!
روري!
- Edrix! - [cheering]
- إدريكس! - [هتاف]
Your best friend, right?
صديقك المفضل، أليس كذلك؟
[chattering]
[ثرثرة]
Hey.
يا.
You've been lost in thought there for too long.
لقد كنت غارقًا في أفكارك هناك لفترة طويلة جدًا.
Do you have a problem?
هل لديك مشكلة؟
[background chattering]
[ثرثرة في الخلفية]
Nothing.
لا شئ.
What's that?
ما هذا؟
[laughs]
[يضحك]
Then why the long face?
ثم لماذا الوجه الطويل؟
[Yuri chuckles]
[يوري يضحك]
That's not funny.
هذا ليس مضحكا.
What is your problem, Jay?
ما هي مشكلتك يا جاي؟
You can share it with me.
يمكنك مشاركتها معي.
It's about Aries.
إنه يتعلق ببرج الحمل.
What happened to him?
ماذا حدث له؟
I feel like I said something bad to him. He just suddenly cried.
أشعر وكأنني قلت له شيئًا سيئًا، فبدأ فجأة في البكاء.
Seriously?
بجد؟
Aries cried?
برج الحمل بكى؟
Yeah.
نعم.
We were just talking about Felix's brother.
كنا نتحدث للتو عن شقيق فيليكس.
What's his name again?
ما اسمه مرة أخرى؟
Per...
لكل...
Percy? Percy! That's it.
بيرسي؟ بيرسي! هذا هو الأمر.
Why were you talking about him?
لماذا كنت تتحدث عنه؟
We weren't actually talking about him. I just asked a question.
لم نكن نتحدث عنه في الواقع، لقد سألت سؤالاً فقط.
Felix and I talked.
تحدثت أنا وفيليكس.
He told me about his brother.
لقد أخبرني عن أخيه.
So, I asked Aries. And then, we fought.
لذا سألت برج الحمل، وبعد ذلك تشاجرنا.
Why? Do you know anything?
لماذا؟ هل تعرف أي شيء؟
Yuri! Jay-jay!
يوري! جاي جاي!
Join the game.
انضم إلى اللعبة.
- Come on! - Quick, join us!
- هيا! - بسرعة، انضم إلينا!
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Let's play the game with them.
دعونا نلعب اللعبة معهم.
Come on! Let's play.
هيا لنلعب.
If you fail to answer, you'll pay five hundred.
إذا فشلت في الإجابة، فسوف تدفع خمسمائة.
- Jay, you go first. - No, he'll do it.
- جاي، أنت اذهب أولاً. - لا، هو سيفعل ذلك.
[chattering]
[ثرثرة]
- Just try one. Just one. - We're gonna guess it.
- فقط جرب واحدة. واحدة فقط. - سوف نخمنها.
Okay. Go, go, go.
حسنًا، اذهب، اذهب، اذهب.
- Go on! Just do it! - Quickly!
- هيا! فقط افعلها! - بسرعة!
[chuckles]
[يضحك]
Do it, quick!
افعلها بسرعة!
- Wait, I'm thinking! - Oh, so you have a brain?
- انتظر، أنا أفكر! - أوه، إذًا لديك عقل؟
Five,
خمسة،
- four, - three,
أربعة، - ثلاثة،
- two, - one!
اثنان، - واحد!
- I'm not doing it then. - [boys groan in disappointment]
- لن أفعل ذلك إذن. - [يتأوه الأولاد بخيبة أمل]
Thank you, ma'am. Your tapa's the best!
شكرا لك سيدتي، طبقك هو الأفضل!
So, sir, when can we get the car?
إذن سيدي، متى يمكننا الحصول على السيارة؟
- The next day. - Next day?
- اليوم التالي. - اليوم التالي؟
- That's too long! - Psst! Hey!
- هذا طويل جدًا! - همسًا! هيا!
Hey, Jay!
مهلا، جاي!
- How are you? - What are you guys up to?
- كيف حالك؟ - ماذا تفعلون يا رفاق؟
My car fucking broke down.
لقد تعطلت سيارتي بشكل فظيع.
So, I had to get it fixed.
لذا، كان لا بد من إصلاحه.
I wanted a ride but I ended up walking, too.
كنت أريد ركوب السيارة ولكنني في النهاية ذهبت سيرًا على الأقدام أيضًا.
Oh, Jay!
أوه، جاي!
The school festival's coming up, right?
المهرجان المدرسي قادم، أليس كذلك؟
That's right!
هذا صحيح!
We still don't have representatives for the contest.
مازلنا لا نملك ممثلين للمسابقة.
We do.
نحن نفعل ذلك.
- Who?
- من؟
Take a good look at each other.
أنظروا جيدا إلى بعضكم البعض.
Mr. Pretty and Ms. Handsome.
السيد الجميل والسيدة الوسيمة.
Well it's obvious I'm gonna be chosen for Ms. Handsome.
حسنًا، من الواضح أنني سأُختار لأكون السيدة الجميلة.
I'm the only girl, so there's no choice.
أنا الفتاة الوحيدة، لذلك ليس هناك خيار.
But Ci-N for Mr. Pretty?
لكن Ci-N للسيد بريتي؟
- I'm not so sure. - Yeah, why me?
- أنا لست متأكدًا تمامًا. - نعم، لماذا أنا؟
You're built like a girl.
لقد تم بناؤها مثل الفتاة.
- You're insane. I'm gonna punch you. - Go on, just try it.
- أنت مجنون. سأضربك. - هيا، فقط حاول ذلك.
Try it!
جربها!
- Alright, I'll kiss you. No malice. - So, what?
- حسنًا، سأقبلك. لا ضغينة. - إذن، ماذا؟
[Jay-jay squeals]
[يصرخ جاي جاي]
- [Ci-N chuckles] - Ci-N, you're so stupid!
- [Ci-N يضحك] - Ci-N، أنت غبي جدًا!
It's too early, but you're already so rowdy.
إنه أمر مبكر جدًا، لكنك صاخب بالفعل.
Why did you do that, bro?
لماذا فعلت ذلك يا أخي؟
- Kiss, kiss, kiss. Game. - Bro, you're so weird.
- قبلة، قبلة، قبلة. لعبة. - يا أخي، أنت غريب جدًا.
Stop with that weird shit, bro.
توقف عن هذا الهراء الغريب، يا أخي.
Please, stop with that weird shit.
من فضلك، توقف عن هذا الهراء الغريب.
Stop! Stop!
توقف! توقف!
You're so annoying, man.
أنت مزعج جدًا، يا رجل.
[Jay-jay screams]
[يصرخ جاي جاي]
- Hey, bro! Jay-jay! - Get off me! Help me!
- يا أخي! جاي جاي! - ابتعد عني! ساعدني!
- Hey! Hey! - Jay-jay!
- هيه! هيه! - جاي جاي!
Hey! Stop! What are you doing?!
مهلا! توقف! ماذا تفعل؟!
Jay!
جاي!
- [beatboxing] - Look at me.
- [الضرب بالبيت] - انظر إلي.
Come on, come on. You first.
هيا، هيا. أنت أولاً.
In heaven, there's an angel.
في الجنة هناك ملاك.
In the sea, there's a shell.
في البحر هناك صدفة.
I saw your bald daddy,
لقد رأيت والدك الأصلع،
- putting on some hair gel. - What's bothering you?
- وضع القليل من جل الشعر. - ما الذي يزعجك؟
[boys getting hyped]
[الأولاد متحمسون]
[Yuri] Aries told Jay-jay about Percy.
[يوري] أخبر أريس جاي جاي عن بيرسي.
Keifer!
كيفر!
What the hell are you shouting about?
ما الذي تصرخ به بحق الجحيم؟
- It's Jay-jay! - What happened to Jay-jay?!
- إنه جاي جاي! - ماذا حدث لجاي جاي؟!
They took her!
لقد أخذوها!
- Ram's people. I'm sure. - What?!
- أهل رام. أنا متأكد. - ماذا؟!
No one's leaving this room.
لا أحد يغادر هذه الغرفة.
It's a trap.
إنه فخ.
We can't just do nothing here, Keifer!
لا يمكننا أن نفعل شيئًا هنا، كايفر!
I know how Ram plays.
أنا أعرف كيف يلعب رام.
He'll lead us into his game,
سيقودنا إلى لعبته،
and then we'll be the ones to end up losing.
وبعد ذلك سوف نكون نحن من سيخسرون في النهاية.
- Then what's your plan?! - We can't just stay here, Keifer!
- إذن ما هي خطتك؟! - لا يمكننا البقاء هنا، كايفر!
I know! I'm thinking!
انا اعرف! انا افكر!
[phone ringing]
[رنين الهاتف]
- What's that? - Who's calling?
- ما هذا؟ - من المتصل؟
It's Ram! It's Ram!
إنه رام! إنه رام!
- Who's that? - Shut your mouth!
- من هذا؟ - أغلق فمك!
- Jay!
- جاي!
[Ram] Hey, hey, hey. Don't be too loud. Can't you see, someone's sleeping?
[رام] هيا، هيا، هيا. لا ترفع صوتك كثيرًا. ألا ترى أن أحدهم نائم؟
Hi, boys! What's up?
مرحبًا يا شباب! ما الأمر؟
- Missed me? - Yeah. A lot.
- هل افتقدتني؟ - نعم، كثيرًا.
Fuck you!
اذهب للجحيم!
You know...
أنت تعرف
our last game was cut a bit short.
لعبتنا الأخيرة كانت قصيرة بعض الشيء.
Let's continue it.
دعونا نستمر.
- Shall we? - What are you gonna do to Jay-jay?!
- هل سنفعل ذلك؟ - ماذا ستفعل بجاي جاي؟!
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I don't really know.
انا لا اعرف حقا.
But I'm pissed at what she did.
لكنني غاضب مما فعلته.
Gosh. I felt cheated.
يا إلهي، لقد شعرت بالخداع.
Speaking of.
بالحديث عن.
You're too noisy. She's awake now.
أنت مزعجة للغاية، إنها مستيقظة الآن.
- Jay! - Jay-jay!
- جاي! - جاي جاي!
Wake up, sleepyhead.
استيقظ أيها النائم.
Ram, what the fuck do you want?!
رام، ماذا تريد بحق الجحيم؟!
Visit your friend.
قم بزيارة صديقك.
But I only accept limited visitors.
ولكنني أقبل عددًا محدودًا من الزوار فقط.
Maybe...
ربما
just four people.
أربعة أشخاص فقط.
Just four?!
أربعة فقط؟!
[Section E boys arguing]
[القسم هـ الأولاد يتجادلون]
- Shut up! - Fuck you, bitch!
- اسكت! - اذهبي إلى الجحيم أيتها العاهرة!
Alright! It'll be just four of us. How many are you?
حسنًا، سنكون أربعة فقط. كم عددكم؟
Hey, now... If I were you, I'll be scrambling my way here.
مهلا، الآن... لو كنت مكانك، سأحاول الوصول إلى هنا.
Look...
ينظر.
I don't like getting bored.
أنا لا أحب الملل.
Stop it!
اوقفها!
- Jay! - You asshole! Son of a bitch!
- جاي! - أيها الأحمق! يا ابن العاهرة!
You know where to find me.
أنت تعرف أين تجدني.
Yuri!
يوري!
You're wasting your strength.
أنت تهدر قوتك.
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
David! Ci-N! Get another car.
ديفيد! سين! احصل على سيارة أخرى.
- The four of us are going. - Are you serious?!
- نحن الأربعة ذاهبون. - هل أنت جاد؟!
We can't risk anything.
لا يمكننا المخاطرة بأي شيء.
Ram said only four.
وقال رام أربعة فقط.
But just like before, we bring a back-up car.
لكن كما في السابق، أحضرنا سيارة احتياطية.
Eren, make sure nobody fucking sees you.
إيرين، تأكد من أن لا يراك أحد.
Let's fucking go!
دعونا نذهب اللعنة!
- Move, quick. - Come on!
- تحرك بسرعة. - هيا!
- What's the plan? - Come on. Let's go!
- ما هي الخطة؟ - هيا، لنذهب!
Hello! Where the hell are you! Come quick!
مرحبًا! أين أنت بحق الجحيم ! تعال بسرعة!
- [Ci-N] Where are you? - We're almost at the parking.
- [Ci-N] أين أنت؟ - لقد وصلنا تقريبًا إلى موقف السيارات.
- We're going to David's car. - Alright. Just be quick.
- سنذهب إلى سيارة ديفيد. - حسنًا، فقط كن سريعًا.
Where the hell is Jay-jay?!
أين هو جاي جاي بحق الجحيم؟!
Ram called Kiko!
رام يسمى كيكو!
I'm sure she got entangled in your mess again!
أنا متأكد من أنها تورطت في فوضاك مرة أخرى!
Mind your own business!
اهتم بأمورك الخاصة!
We're gonna save Jay-jay!
سوف ننقذ جاي جاي!
I'm gonna save my cousin.
سأنقذ ابن عمي.
- We'll go with you. - You can't.
- سنذهب معك. - لا يمكنك.
Ram is asking for four people only.
رام يطلب أربعة أشخاص فقط
Just stay here. You're putting Jay-jay at risk with what you're doing.
فقط ابق هنا، فأنت تعرض جاي جاي للخطر بما تفعله.
- Let's go! - Wait.
- دعنا نذهب! - انتظر.
- Let's just report it. - No. I know Ram.
- دعنا نبلغ عن ذلك. - لا، أنا أعرف رام.
Jay-jay will be in more danger if we do that.
سيكون جاي جاي في خطر أكبر إذا فعلنا ذلك.
And then what?
وبعد ذلك ماذا؟
Aren't you gonna tell your brother?
ألا تنوي أن تخبر أخاك؟
Where are you, guys? What's taking so long?
أين أنتم يا شباب؟ ما الذي يستغرق كل هذا الوقت؟
[Ci-N] Wait up! We're almost there. Just got stuck at the stoplight.
[Ci-N] انتظر! لقد وصلنا تقريبًا. لقد علقت للتو عند إشارة المرور.
- Just get here fast. - [Ci-N] Okay, okay.
- فقط تعال إلى هنا بسرعة. - [Ci-N] حسنًا، حسنًا.
I'm gonna fuck them up if they touch her. I swear.
سأقوم بإفسادهم إذا لمسوها. أقسم بذلك.
Keifer, I need to ask you something.
كايفر، أريد أن أسألك شيئًا.
Do you have to ask it now?
هل يجب عليك أن تسأله الآن؟
Did something happen between you and Jay-jay at the Horror House?
هل حدث شيء بينك وبين جاي جاي في بيت الرعب؟
Wait, let me ask you first.
انتظر، دعني أسألك أولاً.
Do you like Jay-jay?
هل تحب جاي جاي؟
Do you have feelings for her?
هل لديك مشاعر تجاهها؟
Yes.
نعم.
I think I'm falling for her.
أعتقد أنني أقع في حبها.
Are you out of your mind?
هل أنت خارج عقلك؟
You know we have a plan.
أنت تعلم أن لدينا خطة.
Is this still part of your plan?
هل هذا لا يزال جزءا من خطتك؟
Everything that happened at the amusement park.
كل ما حدث في مدينة الملاهي.
The incident with Aries.
الحادثة مع برج الحمل.
And now, us saving her from Ram.
والآن، نحن ننقذها من رام.
Of course.
بالطبع.
Are you starting to doubt me?
هل بدأت تشك بي؟
You saw how worried Aries was.
لقد رأيت مدى قلق برج الحمل.
He cares about Jay-jay. It's still part of the plan.
إنه يهتم بجاي جاي، وهذا لا يزال جزءًا من الخطة.
Is that true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Because I can see that your concern for her is becoming real.
لأنني أستطيع أن أرى أن قلقك عليها أصبح حقيقيا.
Why are you doing this, Keifer?
لماذا تفعل هذا يا كايفر؟
You know I need her for my plan, Yuri.
أنت تعرف أنني بحاجة إليها في خطتي، يوري.
- Where the hell are they?! - Let's go! You're too slow!
- أين هم بحق الجحيم؟! - دعنا نذهب! أنت بطيء جدًا!
Come on! Let's go!
هيا لنذهب!
Well, well, well...
حسنًا، حسنًا، حسنًا...
Look at the people gathered here.
أنظر إلى الناس المتجمعين هنا.
Hey... you got some visitors.
مهلا... لقد حصلت على بعض الزوار.
Hey!
يا!
Why so serious?
لماذا الجدية؟
You, too!
أنت أيضاً!
Just chill!
فقط استرخي!
You did that on purpose, asshole!
لقد فعلت ذلك عمدا أيها الأحمق!
Don't overreact.
لا تبالغ في رد الفعل.
I just thought maybe you'd like to jump again.
لقد فكرت للتو أنك ربما ترغب بالقفز مرة أخرى.
We're here. What the hell do you want?
نحن هنا. ماذا تريد بحق الجحيم؟
I was left hanging.
لقد تركت معلقا.
Remember? And besides...
تذكر؟ وبالإضافة إلى ذلك.
I got this itch.
لقد حصلت على هذه الحكة.
I always want to see people fighting.
أريد دائمًا رؤية الناس يقاتلون.
Boys!
الأولاد!
Look. They're gonna beat up your friends.
انظر، إنهم سوف يضربون أصدقائك.
That's it?
هذا كل شيء؟
You're too few.
أنتم قليلون جداً.
Hey. Don't be so arrogant.
مهلا، لا تكن مغرورًا جدًا.
Let's see if you can make your way up here.
دعونا نرى ما إذا كان بإمكانك الوصول إلى هنا.
Bye-bye!
وداعا وداعا!
Jasper Jean Mariano!
جاسبر جان ماريانو!
Wait for me!
الانتظار لي!
Come on! Move!
هيا تحرك!
So...
لذا...
- Let's go. - Let's get to it!
- دعنا نذهب. - دعنا نبدأ!
Wait up!
انتظر!
Wait! Hey!
انتظر! مهلا!
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
What?!
ماذا؟!
Did it start yet?
هل بدأت بعد؟
Fuck you!
اذهب للجحيم!
- What did you say?! - Fuck you!
- ماذا قلت؟! - اذهب إلى الجحيم!
Are you done, dude?
هل إنتهيت يا صديقي؟
Out of my way.
ابتعد عن طريقي.
Jay!
جاي!
Keifer?...
كيفر؟
Don't!
لا!
What do you take me for, some stupid fool?
ماذا تظنني، أيها الأحمق الغبي؟
I'm ready for you, bro!
أنا مستعد لك يا أخي!
Stop it, please!
اوقفها من فضلك!
Stop it, please! Stop...
توقف من فضلك! توقف...
Stop it!
اوقفها!
You're begging?
هل أنت تتوسل؟
Huh?
هاه؟
For this guy?
لهذا الرجل؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Is he your boyfriend?
هل هو صديقك؟
Don't cry, Jay...
لا تبكي يا جاي...
Don't cry.
لا تبكي.
[Jay-jay cries]
[جاي جاي يبكي]
You're a coward.
أنت جبان.
I don't care about what you say.
لا يهمني ما تقوله.
It's tough fighting you!
من الصعب القتال معك!
Of all my men, none have defeated you.
من بين جميع رجالي، لم يهزمك أحد.
Cause you're so fucking weak.
لأنك ضعيف جدًا.
Huh? Weak?
هاه؟ ضعيف؟
[grunts in pain]
[يئن من الألم]
Weak!
ضعيف!
Huh?
هاه؟
[Jay-jay screams]
[يصرخ جاي جاي]
Keifer!
كيفر!
Jay! Get out of here.
جاي! اخرج من هنا.
Run, Jay!
أركض يا جاي!
- No, I won't leave you! - Please, Jay...
- لا، لن أتركك! - من فضلك، جاي...
Just get out of here, please...
فقط اخرج من هنا، من فضلك...
No! I won't leave you!
لا! لن أتركك!
- Just leave me... - Get up! Let's go!
- فقط اتركني... - انهض! دعنا نذهب!
- Come on, let's go! - Run, Jay, please.
- هيا، دعنا نذهب! - أركض، جاي، من فضلك.
Come here...
تعال الى هنا...
[Jay-jay screaming]
[جاي جاي يصرخ]
- Let go of me! - You bitch!
-اتركني! -يا عاهرة!
Jay!
جاي!
Jay, that's enough! Stop!
جاي، هذا يكفي! توقف!
Please.
لو سمحت.
Jay, stop.
جاي، توقف.
Jay, breathe, breathe. Breathe, Jay.
جاي، تنفس، تنفس، جاي.
Breathe. Relax, I'm here. It's me. It's me.
تنفس، استرخي، أنا هنا، أنا هنا.
I'm here, Jay.
انا هنا، جاي.
Relax, I'm here.
استرخي، أنا هنا.
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
Relax. Relax, I'm here.
استرخي، استرخي، أنا هنا.
It's me, relax.
أنا، استرخي.
It's okay. Just breathe.
لا بأس، فقط تنفس.
Just breathe.
فقط تنفس.
Just breathe, Jay, I'm here.
فقط تنفس يا جاي، أنا هنا.
I'm here. It's me. It's okay. Just breathe.
أنا هنا، أنا هنا، لا بأس، فقط تنفس.
Just breathe.
فقط تنفس.
Relax.
يستريح.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
It's okay, It's okay.
لا بأس، لا بأس.
Keifer?
كيفر؟
It's me.
هذا أنا.
Jay, it's me.
جاي، أنا.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
You're good.
أنت جيدة أو أنت طيب.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Did I do that to him?
هل فعلت ذلك له؟
I must have done it. Cyrus was also in this state when I woke up.
لا بد أنني فعلت ذلك. كان سايروس أيضًا في هذه الحالة عندما استيقظت.
What did I do to him?
ماذا فعلت له؟
Did I kill him?
هل قتلته؟
- No, no, no, no, no. - Is he dead?
- لا، لا، لا، لا، لا. - هل هو ميت؟
- [Jay-jay crying] - He's still alive.
- [جاي جاي يبكي] - لا يزال على قيد الحياة.
He's alive.
إنه على قيد الحياة.
He's still breathing.
مازال يتنفس.
You're just protecting yourself, Jay.
أنت تحمي نفسك فقط، جاي.
Look at me.
انظر إليَّ.
You're okay.
أنت بخير.
You're okay. Just breathe.
أنت بخير، فقط تنفس.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Jay!
جاي!
- Damn! - He's still breathing?
- اللعنة! - هل لا يزال يتنفس؟
Is this guy still alive?
هل هذا الرجل لا يزال على قيد الحياة؟
We got every last one of them.
لقد حصلنا على كل واحد منهم.
Aries is outside.
برج الحمل في الخارج.
He doesn't wanna back down.
إنه لا يريد التراجع.
He's so worried about Jay.
إنه قلق جدًا بشأن جاي.
Keifer.
كيفر.
Can we talk?
أيمكننا أن تحدث؟
I need to know what happened.
أريد أن أعرف ماذا حدث.
Yeah.
نعم.
Aries.
بُرْجُ الحَمَل.
Where's Keifer?
أين كايفر؟
He's outside. Talking to Angelo.
إنه بالخارج ويتحدث مع أنجيلو.
Aries.
بُرْجُ الحَمَل.
Why?
لماذا؟
What did I do to your father before?
ماذا فعلت لأبيك من قبل؟
I don't want to talk about that.
لا أريد التحدث عن هذا.
Did I hurt him too?
هل أذيته أيضاً؟
Just like what I did to Cyrus and Ram?
تمامًا كما فعلت مع سايروس ورام؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
Did I almost kill him too?
هل كدت أقتله أيضًا؟
- Did I also— - Stop it!
- هل فعلت ذلك أيضًا؟ - توقف!
Stop asking questions about him.
توقف عن طرح الأسئلة عنه.
Aries! What's happening here?
برج الحمل! ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Aries. What are you doing?
برج الحمل ماذا تفعل؟
He hasn't done anything wrong.
لم يفعل أي شيء خطأ.
Aries.
بُرْجُ الحَمَل.
Jay, are you okay?
جاي، هل أنت بخير؟
Jay!
جاي!
I'm glad you're okay! I thought we lost you, Jay!
أنا سعيد أنك بخير! اعتقدت أننا فقدناك، جاي!
- This kid is being overly-dramatic. - Talk to me, Jay!
- هذا الطفل يبالغ في الدراما. - تحدث معي، جاي!
Ouch! You're making the pain worse for me.
آآآه! أنت تجعل الألم أسوأ بالنسبة لي.
Sorry.
آسف.
What happened there?
ماذا حدث هناك؟
She was asking what happened to Dad.
لقد سألت ماذا حدث لأبي.
What happened? And why didn't you inform me immediately?
ماذا حدث ولماذا لم تخبرني على الفور؟
You let Keifer do all the work?
هل سمحت لكيفر أن يقوم بكل العمل؟
I just didn't know what to do.
لم أعرف ماذا أفعل.
You didn't even think of finding her too?
ولم تفكر حتى في العثور عليها أيضًا؟
- I did look for her. - You should've come with them.
- لقد بحثت عنها. - كان ينبغي عليك أن تأتي معهم.
She is your—
إنها لك...
She's your cousin!
إنها ابنة عمك!
You should be the first to look out for her.
ينبغي عليك أن تكون أول من يبحث عنها.
Sorry.
آسف.
Because it happened again,
لأنه حدث مرة أخرى،
I think it's better to take Jay-jay to a psychiatrist.
أعتقد أنه من الأفضل أخذ جاي جاي إلى طبيب نفسي.
Keifer explained to me what she did.
لقد شرحت لي كايفر ما فعلته.
She can't remember a thing.
لا تستطيع أن تتذكر أي شيء.
That's not normal.
هذا ليس طبيعيا.
We need to be serious in getting her the help she needs.
نحن بحاجة إلى أن نكون جادين في منحها المساعدة التي تحتاجها.
You decide. You're her guardian after all.
أنت من يقرر، فأنت الوصي عليها بعد كل شيء.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Hello sir, one of our investors are threatening to pull out.
مرحبًا سيدي، أحد المستثمرين لدينا يهدد بالانسحاب.
No. I won't allow him to pull out.
لا. لن اسمح له بالانسحاب.
Set a meeting now. I'm on my way.
حدد موعدًا للاجتماع الآن. أنا في طريقي.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Aries. I have to go. Something came up.
برج الحمل، يجب أن أذهب، لقد حدث أمر ما.
Take care of Jay.
اعتني بجاي.
Excuse me, miss. Where is the room of Jasper Jean Mariano?
عذرا سيدتي أين غرفة جاسبر جان ماريانو؟
- I'll just check, ma'am. - Okay.
- سأتحقق من ذلك سيدتي. - حسنًا.
Aries!
بُرْجُ الحَمَل!
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
I'm visiting my daughter.
أنا أزور ابنتي.
She needs her mom now.
إنها تحتاج أمها الآن.
Is that a joke?
هل هذه مزحة؟
It's not funny.
إنه ليس مضحكا.
Aries, I just want to see Jay-jay.
برج الحمل، أريد فقط رؤية جاي جاي.
It's been so long since we last talked.
لقد مر وقت طويل منذ آخر مرة تحدثنا فيها.
And I want to let her know, I'm getting married—
وأريد أن أخبرها أنني سأتزوج..
Again?
مرة أخرى؟
Aren't you getting tired of this?
ألا تشعر بالتعب من هذا؟
You think Jay-jay would be happy once she hears this?
هل تعتقد أن جاي جاي سوف يكون سعيدًا عندما يسمع هذا؟
Don't you dare raise your voice at me.
لا تجرؤ على رفع صوتك علي.
You might be forgetting who I really am.
ربما أنك نسيت من أنا حقًا.
Let me guess.
دعني أخمن.
You still haven't told her the truth.
لم تخبرها الحقيقة بعد.
That's none of your business.
هذا لا يعنيك .
I'll tell her eventually, but not today.
سأخبرها في النهاية، ولكن ليس اليوم.
You make sure of that.
تأكد من ذلك.
Or else, I'll tell her myself.
وإلا سأخبرها بنفسي.
You have the guts to threaten me?
هل لديك الجرأة لتهديدي؟
If you're truly concerned for Jay-jay,
إذا كنت مهتمًا حقًا بجاي جاي،
you wouldn't show your face here.
لن تظهر وجهك هنا.
Because you know she'll just get hurt even more.
لأنك تعلم أنها سوف تتأذى أكثر فأكثر.
[background chattering]
[ثرثرة في الخلفية]
Jay-jay.
جاي جاي.
Huh?
هاه؟
For you.
لك.
Please smile.
من فضلك ابتسم.
Give us a smile!
أعطنا ابتسامة!
[teasing]
[إغاظة]
She's going to smile!
إنها سوف تبتسم!
- Hey, here's food. - Thank you.
- مرحباً، إليك الطعام. - شكرا لك.
Eat up.
تناول الطعام.
Ouch!
آخ!
Can I?
هل يمكنني؟
Why are you still down?
لماذا لا تزال مكتئبا؟
Is it because the pancake's burnt?
هل هذا بسبب حرق الفطيرة؟
That's the 30th time you asked me since I left the hospital.
هذه هي المرة الثلاثين التي تسألني فيها منذ أن غادرت المستشفى.
If every question of yours was paid, maybe I could buy a pair of shoes now.
إذا تم دفع جميع أسئلتك، ربما أستطيع شراء زوج من الأحذية الآن.
You know, I won't bother asking you if you're not like this.
أنت تعلم، لن أزعج نفسي بالسؤال إذا لم تكن هكذا.
You can share your problems with me, okay?
يمكنك مشاركة مشاكلك معي، حسنًا؟
[indistinct chattering]
[ثرثرة غير واضحة]
Guys!
شباب!
Section E!
القسم هـ!
- Section E! - Hey, quiet down!
- القسم هـ! - مهلا، اهدأ!
Hey, they're calling Section E with H.
مهلا، إنهم يطلقون على القسم E اسم H.
The committee is asking for the names of the participants.
تطلب اللجنة أسماء المشاركين.
- Committee? - What committee?
- لجنة؟ - أي لجنة؟
Committee!
لجنة!
They're asking who's gonna participate in the festival.
إنهم يتساءلون من سيشارك في المهرجان.
- What? - Repeat what you said.
- ماذا؟ - كرر ما قلته.
Committee. Committee, are you satisfied?
اللجنة، اللجنة، هل أنتم راضون؟
Ahhh.
آآآه.
As we've discussed, Ci-N and Jay-jay
كما ناقشنا، Ci-N وJay-jay
will represent us for Mr. Pretty and Ms. Handsome.
سيمثلنا السيد الجميل والسيدة الوسيمة.
- Wow! - Mr. Pretty!
- واو! - السيد الجميل!
[Section E getting hyped]
[القسم E يزداد إثارة]
- Wait up, this one's about to cry. - Who?
- انتظر، هذا على وشك البكاء. - من؟
Hey, how about for the Battle of the Bands?
مهلا، ماذا عن معركة الفرق الموسيقية؟
There you go.
ها أنت ذا.
Keifer and I haven't talked about it yet.
لم نتحدث أنا وكيفير عن هذا الأمر بعد.
You have a band?
هل لديك فرقة موسيقية؟
Well... we used to play before.
حسنًا... لقد كنا نلعب من قبل.
Keifer was the main vocalist. Blaster and I are on guitars.
كان كايفر هو المغني الرئيسي، وأنا وبلاستر نعزف على الجيتار.
Edrix on drums. Rory on bass.
إدريكس على الطبول. روري على الباس.
Felix on the piano.
فيليكس على البيانو.
I see.
أرى.
But that was a long time ago.
ولكن ذلك كان منذ زمن طويل.
Before the incident with Ella.
قبل الحادثة مع ايلا.
That's a shame.
إنه لأمر مؤسف.
Wait, how about the dance contest?
انتظر، ماذا عن مسابقة الرقص؟
- Count me in! - I'm game for that!
- اعتبرني معك! - أنا مستعد لذلك!
[boys shuttering]
[الأولاد يصرخون]
- How much is the cash prize? - There you go again!
- كم قيمة الجائزة النقدية؟ - ها أنت ذا مرة أخرى!
I was merely asking!
كنت أسأل فقط!
Guys, wait. There's also a singing contest.
يا شباب، انتظروا. هناك أيضًا مسابقة غناء.
Who wants to join the singing contest?
من يريد الانضمام إلى مسابقة الغناء؟
[discussing]
[مناقشة]
Come with me.
تعال معي.
What?
ماذا؟
Just a moment.
لحظة واحدة.
[background chattering]
[ثرثرة في الخلفية]
- I'll go first? - Are you scared? Just get in.
- سأذهب أولاً؟ - هل أنت خائف؟ فقط ادخل.
Hey. Are you planning something bad to me?!
مهلا، هل تخطط لشيء سيء لي؟!
Who are these people?
من هم هؤلاء الناس؟
Past Section E.
القسم الماضي هـ
From the year 1994 to the present year.
من عام 1994 إلى العام الحالي.
Why do you have something like this?
لماذا لديك شيئا مثل هذا؟
The truth is we didn't know.
الحقيقة أننا لم نكن نعرف.
We just found this place when we moved into the room downstairs.
لقد وجدنا هذا المكان للتو عندما انتقلنا إلى الغرفة في الطابق السفلي.
And it's all filled with pictures of juniors and seniors, so...
وكلها مليئة بصور الصغار والكبار، لذلك...
We thought to join in as well, since...
لقد فكرنا في الانضمام أيضًا، منذ
we're also Section E.
نحن أيضًا القسم E.
Maybe they're also assholes like the Section E of today.
ربما هم أيضًا أغبياء مثل القسم E اليوم.
Crazy and troublesome... just like Keifer.
مجنون ومزعج... تمامًا مثل كايفر.
Is that?...
هل هذا؟
That's Angelo, isn't it?
هذا أنجيلو، أليس كذلك؟
Yeah.
نعم.
He's from Section E too?
هل هو من القسم E أيضا؟
He was the best and most powerful president in Section E.
وكان أفضل وأقوى رئيس في القسم (هـ).
Really? How did you know?
حقا؟ كيف عرفت؟
Believe it or not, half of this town knows him well.
صدق أو لا تصدق، نصف سكان هذه المدينة يعرفونه جيدًا.
Even other schools are afraid to visit just because of him.
حتى المدارس الأخرى تخاف من زيارته فقط بسببه.
Cool.
رائع.
Wanna put up your picture on the wall?
هل تريد وضع صورتك على الحائط؟
Me?
أنا؟
Why?
لماذا؟
You don't want to?
أنت لا تريد ذلك؟
You're Section E.
أنت القسم E.
I'm Section E.
أنا القسم E.
See?
يرى؟
You look better when you're smiling.
تبدو أفضل عندما تبتسم.
You too.
أنت أيضاً.
You look better.
تبدو أفضل.
Just let me know if you want to put your picture up.
فقط اسمح لي أن أعرف إذا كنت تريد وضع صورتك.
I'll let you borrow the key.
سأسمح لك باستعارة المفتاح.
[nods]
[يومئ برأسه]
Let's go. They're waiting for us.
هيا بنا، إنهم ينتظروننا.
Ah, Keifer.
اه، كيفر.
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Tss!
تسس!
What an asshole.
يا له من أحمق!
Oh. What's up with you guys?
أوه، ما الأمر معكم يا رفاق؟
Just watch.
فقط شاهد.
Why aren't you moving?
لماذا لا تتحرك؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Boys.
الأولاد.
Five, four, three, two...
خمسة، أربعة، ثلاثة، اثنان...
[singing]
[الغناء]
[Jay-jay laughing]
[جاي جاي يضحك]
Yuri?!
يوري؟!
Wow.
رائع.
Wow. Is that what you've been doing to your girlfriend?!
واو، هل هذا ما كنت تفعله مع صديقتك؟!
Look at those two by the table!
أنظر إلى هذين الشخصين بجانب الطاولة!
That's what love does to a person.
هذا ما يفعله الحب بالانسان .
So powerful. Isn't your dance too aggressive, Ci-N?
إنها قوية جدًا. أليس رقصك عدوانيًا للغاية، Ci-N؟
Is this really happening? Talk about being the Best President.
هل يحدث هذا حقًا؟ تحدث عن كونك أفضل رئيس.
I think he's in front me now, dancing together with his fellow assholes.
أعتقد أنه أمامي الآن، يرقص مع زملائه الحمقى.
[singing continues]
[يستمر الغناء]
What is this?!
ما هذا؟!
Alright! You can stop now!
حسنًا، يمكنك التوقف الآن!
You guys have a future as dancers!
لديكم مستقبل كراقصين!
[singing continues]
[يستمر الغناء]
[Jay-jay laughing]
[جاي جاي يضحك]
[Ci-N and Calix singing]
[سين وكاليكس يغنيان]
Hey. What are you doing?
مهلا، ماذا تفعل؟
You're not do-
أنت لا تفعل ذلك.
Hey, that's mine!
مهلا، هذا لي!
You're so selfish! As if you didn't eat all the chocolates at home.
أنت أنانية جدًا! وكأنك لم تأكلي كل الشوكولاتة الموجودة في المنزل.
- You're overreacting. - Hey, Denzel!
- أنت تبالغ في رد فعلك. - مهلا، دينزل!
How's your work going at Eman's place?
كيف تسير الأمور في عملك في منزل إيمان؟
I'm doing okay since Eman's there with me.
أنا بخير منذ أن أصبح إيمان معي.
Tiring but I gotta do it for Grace.
مرهق ولكن لا بد لي من القيام بذلك من أجل جريس.
Very good. I'm glad you listened to us.
جيد جدًا، أنا سعيد لأنك استمعت إلينا.
Very good, Denzel.
جيد جدًا، دينزل.
Wait.
انتظر.
listen up, you guys.
استمعوا يا شباب.
- We're gonna talk about the festival. - Hey, it's the festival!
- سوف نتحدث عن المهرجان. - مهلا، إنه المهرجان!
[Section E getting hyped]
[القسم E يزداد إثارة]
First things first.
أولاً وقبل كل شيء.
First, the participants. Second, the tasks they assigned to us.
أولاً، المشاركون. ثانياً، المهام التي كلفونا بها.
Write it down.
اكتبها
Alright, I'll do it. Come with me. I'm bad at memories.
حسنًا، سأفعل ذلك. تعال معي. أنا سيئ في تذكر الذكريات.
It's memorization, dumbass.
إنه الحفظ، أيها الأحمق.
Don't write on the wall. Don't vandalize.
لا تكتب على الحائط، لا تخرب.
Jay, look at the walls around us.
جاي، أنظر إلى الجدران حولنا.
- Yeah, see that? - Read it over there. "Mayet is ugly."
- نعم، هل رأيت ذلك؟ - اقرأه هناك. "ماييت قبيحة".
[laughs]
[يضحك]
Okay, Monday.
حسناً، يوم الاثنين.
Monday.
الاثنين.
The parade will be on Monday.
سيكون العرض يوم الاثنين.
Visitors from other schools will come.
سيأتي زوار من مدارس أخرى.
And the representatives and players will be introduced.
وسيتم تقديم الممثلين واللاعبين.
Which means, there will be no contest on this day.
وهذا يعني أنه لن يكون هناك أي منافسة في هذا اليوم.
As for the tasks, since the Dance Contest will be held the next day,
أما بالنسبة للمهام، بما أن مسابقة الرقص ستقام في اليوم التالي،
our representatives are exempted from the tasks
ممثلينا معفون من المهام.
Just do your task the next night.
فقط قم بمهمتك في الليلة التالية.
He talks too quickly.
إنه يتحدث بسرعة كبيرة.
Unlike before, we will divide the duties into three groups.
على عكس السابق، سنقوم بتقسيم الواجبات إلى ثلاث مجموعات.
So that others can take some rest.
لكي يتمكن الآخرون من أخذ قسط من الراحة.
Patrol Duty will start by 7:00 PM to 7:00 AM.
ستبدأ مهمة الدورية من الساعة 7 مساءً حتى الساعة 7 صباحًا.
First group: Rory, Kit, Mayo.
المجموعة الأولى: روري، كيت، مايو.
Eman, Calix and Josh.
إيمان وكاليكس وجوش.
We're on night duty? But there's ghosts in there.
نحن في مهمة ليلية؟ ولكن هناك أشباح هناك.
- Boo. - Son of a bitch.
- بوو. - ابن العاهرة.
- [laughing] - Are you afraid?
- [يضحك] - هل أنت خائف؟
No I'm not, fuck you!
لا أنا لست كذلك، اذهب إلى الجحيم!
It's Josh's favorite part!
إنه الجزء المفضل لدى جوش!
Part? Why?
جزء؟ لماذا؟
- Josh has a third eye. Didn't you know? - Huh?
- جوش لديه عين ثالثة. ألم تكن تعلم؟ - هاه؟
- Ask him if there's a ghost in here. - Why? Right there!
- اسأله إن كان هناك شبح هنا. - لماذا؟ هناك!
Hey!
يا!
[laughing]
[يضحك]
Hey. Quiet, quiet.
مهلا. هدوء، هدوء.
Second group: from 11:00 PM to 3:00 AM.
المجموعة الثانية : من الساعة 11:00 مساءً إلى الساعة 3:00 صباحاً.
- Well... - Yuri. Eren. Me. Ci-N. David. And Jay-jay.
- حسنًا... - يوري. إيرين. أنا. سي-إن. ديفيد. وجاي-جاي.
Garbage collecting will start when the program ends.
سيتم البدء بجمع القمامة عند انتهاء البرنامج.
The rest of the class that I did not mention will be the third group.
The rest of the class that I did not mention will be the third group.
Set-up is the same the following days.
Set-up is the same the following days.
Unless you have an event the next day.
Unless you have an event the next day.
No need to attend the duty.
No need to attend the duty.
Tuesday. Dance contest.
Tuesday. Dance contest.
- Do we have representatives for this? - Us!
- Do we have representatives for this? - Us!
Hey, me!
Hey, me!
Me, Calix, Eren, Drew, and Blaster.
Me, Calix, Eren, Drew, and Blaster.
Wait a minute,
Wait a minute,
is it okay if Ci-N joins the dance contest and Mr. Pretty?
is it okay if Ci-N joins the dance contest and Mr. Pretty?
That's fine. It wasn't mentioned in the rules.
That's fine. It wasn't mentioned in the rules.
Battle of the bands.
Battle of the bands.
Shall we do this?
Shall we do this?
We don't have any other representative.
We don't have any other representative.
Choose a proper song.
Choose a proper song.
Yes!
Yes!
Singing contest.
Singing contest.
Anyone with a hidden talent, come out now.
Anyone with a hidden talent, come out now.
Keep hiding.
Keep hiding.
Do it for the fam, Yuri.
Do it for the fam, Yuri.
Do it for the fam!
Do it for the fam!
Why don't  you do it? You sing, right?
Why don't you do it? You sing, right?
Yeah, Yuri. Do it. So I can hear you sing.
Yeah, Yuri. Do it. So I can hear you sing.
Show it!
Show it!
Alright, I'll do it.
Alright, I'll do it.
[Section E getting hyped]
[Section E getting hyped]
As we already discussed, Ci-N will join Mr. Pretty and Jay-jay for Ms. Handsome.
As we already discussed, Ci-N will join Mr. Pretty and Jay-jay for Ms. Handsome.
In the morning, there's the Inter-year.
In the morning, there's the Inter-year.
In the evening, the contest for grade-level representatives.
In the evening, the contest for grade-level representatives.
Have you prepared your introduction and talent?
Have you prepared your introduction and talent?
- Right. - Huh?
- Right. - Huh?
Is there such a thing?
Is there such a thing?
Yeah, there is.
Yeah, there is.
- I already have one! Wanna hear it? - Don't bother!
- I already have one! Wanna hear it? - Don't bother!
- Everyone! - No need! We don't wanna hear!
- Everyone! - No need! We don't wanna hear!
Hello. I'm Ci-N Peralta.
Hello. I'm Ci-N Peralta.
I'm the representative of Section E.
I'm the representative of Section E.
And I believe in the saying...
And I believe in the saying...
If "your future" is big...
If "your future" is big...
All the boys would like to dig!
All the boys would like to dig!
[cheering]
[cheering]
Oh, wow. My view in life has changed.
Oh, wow. My view in life has changed.
Dude you're so embarrassing.
Dude you're so embarrassing.
Disgusting. Are you serious? Are you really saying that in front of everyone?
Disgusting. Are you serious? Are you really saying that in front of everyone?
Yeah. Why not?
Yeah. Why not?
You didn't reach me.
You didn't reach me.
[laughs]
[laughs]
- Here's another one! - Her legs are too short!
- Here's another one! - Her legs are too short!
- Jay, prepare your introduction too. - Yeah.
- Jay, prepare your introduction too. - Yeah.
- Me! I got one too! - Stop it!
- Me! I got one too! - Stop it!
Who's gonna take you home? Keifer and Yuri are both free.
Who's gonna take you home? Keifer and Yuri are both free.
It's okay. I'm gonna stop by somewhere. I'm good.
It's okay. I'm gonna stop by somewhere. I'm good.
Are you sure, Jay?
Are you sure, Jay?
I can take you to the terminal.
I can take you to the terminal.
[background chattering]
[background chattering]
It's okay. It's not that far.
It's okay. It's not that far.
Okay.
Okay.
[background chattering]
[background chattering]
Good morning.
Good morning.
Ice cream, ice cream.
Ice cream, ice cream.
What's good in here?
What's good in here?
Chocolate, cheese, ube...
Chocolate, cheese, ube...
Jay-jay?
Jay-jay?
Yes?
Yes?
Jay-jay, it is you!
Jay-jay, it is you!
You're grown already. How are you?
You're grown already. How are you?
I'm fine. Who are you again?
I'm fine. Who are you again?
You really don't recognize me. So, it's true.
You really don't recognize me. So, it's true.
Don't be afraid. You know me.
Don't be afraid. You know me.
I was your mom's ex-husband.
I was your mom's ex-husband.
I'm sorry, but I don't really know you.
I'm sorry, but I don't really know you.
It's okay. Let me apologize to you.
It's okay. Let me apologize to you.
For the wrong things I did when I was your mom's husband.
For the wrong things I did when I was your mom's husband.
I was hooked up on my vices back then.
I was hooked up on my vices back then.
So whenever I see you, you take the receiving end of my anger.
So whenever I see you, you take the receiving end of my anger.
But believe me, now that I have a child of my own, I regretted everything I did.
لكن صدقني، الآن بعد أن أصبح لدي طفل ، أشعر بالندم على كل ما فعلته.
If you still can't remember, I'm Tony dela Cruz.
إذا كنت لا تزال لا تستطيع أن تتذكر، أنا توني ديلا كروز.
I'm sorry, I really don't. I better go.
أنا آسف، لا أريد ذلك حقًا. من الأفضل أن أذهب.
I'm much worse. I'm trapped in a past I can't remember.
أنا أسوأ بكثير، فأنا عالق في الماضي الذي لا أستطيع تذكره.
Jay!
جاي!
Jay, what happened?!
جاي، ماذا حدث؟!
- Yuri! - Why are you running?
- يوري! - لماذا تركض؟
A man approached me.
اقترب مني رجل.
He said he was my mother's ex, but... I can't remember him.
لقد قال أنه كان حبيب أمي السابق، ولكن... لا أستطيع أن أتذكره.
If you can't remember, there must be a reason.
إذا لم تتمكن من التذكر، فلا بد من وجود سبب.
There are things... people... that are better off forgotten.
هناك أشياء... أشخاص... من الأفضل أن ننساها.
Yuri's right.
يوري على حق.
Maybe that's why I've forgotten all of my traumatic memories.
ربما لهذا السبب نسيت كل ذكرياتي المؤلمة.
But the incident with Ram... Maybe I won't ever forget it.
لكن الحادثة مع رام... ربما لن أنساها أبدًا.
Because aside from fear, I felt safe and secured in the feeling...
لأنه بجانب الخوف، كنت أشعر بالأمان والطمأنينة في الشعور...
That everything will be okay.
أن كل شيء سيكون على ما يرام.
Jay?
جاي؟
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Because of Keifer.
بسبب كايفر.
There's someone too excited! Me!
هناك شخص متحمس جدًا! أنا!
As always, I'm your DJ...
كما هو الحال دائمًا، أنا دي جي الخاص بك...
And I'll be with you throughout the next five days.
وسأكون معكم طيلة الأيام الخمسة المقبلة.
Having fun without me?
هل تستمتع بدوني؟
You want that? I'll win this game for you.
هل تريد ذلك؟ سأفوز بهذه اللعبة من أجلك.
Boring game.
لعبة مملة.
You're a sore loser.
أنت خاسر سيء.
I'll win you something better.
سأفوز لك بشيء أفضل.
- And what is that? - Battle of the Bands.
- وما هذا؟ - معركة الفرق الموسيقية.
Seems like, oh!
يبدو مثل، أوه!
- Foul!
- خطأ!
Coach! Coach!
مدرب! مدرب!
Coach, you can see you don't have many players left!
يا مدرب، يمكنك أن ترى أنه ليس لديك الكثير من اللاعبين المتبقيين!
- Can you do it? - Yes, I can!
- هل تستطيع فعل ذلك؟ - نعم أستطيع!
- Shoot that ball!
- أطلق النار على تلك الكرة!
Evans at number eight, pass into Felix Collins!
إيفانز في الرقم ثمانية، مرر الكرة إلى فيليكس كولينز!
For the win!
من أجل الفوز!
And the next to showcase their talents are...
والقادمون لإظهار مواهبهم هم...
From Section E.
من القسم هـ.
So handsome, Keif--
وسيم جدا ، كيف
I mean, all of them.
أعني، كلهم.
Who's that unlucky guy you're having feelings for?
من هو هذا الرجل غير المحظوظ الذي لديك مشاعر تجاهه؟
You see how Keifer treats me.
ترى كيف يعاملني كايفر.
So, Keifer's the one you were talking about.
إذن، كايفير هو الشخص الذي كنت تتحدث عنه.
Don't tell it to anyone. It's a secret.
لا تخبر أحداً بهذا الأمر، فهو سر.
Keifer, Jay-jay.
كايفر، جاي جاي.
KeiJay.
كيجاي.
I told you it's a secret.
لقد قلت لك أن هذا سر.
- Your voice is too loud! - JayFer...
- صوتك مرتفع جدًا! - جايفير...